《黑吃黑》第三季 第二集
Banshee S03E02
你怎么才来  我都快忙死了
Where were you? I'm drowning out here.
抱歉  两份薄煎饼
Sorry. Two short stacks.
我给你们再拿点糖浆
Let me get you guys some more syrup.
-最近如何  -再好不过了
- Enjoying the show? - Best seat in the house.
你干嘛啊
What are you doing?
回见
I'll catch you later.
话说我们什么时候一起开车来上班啊
So when are we gonna stop driving separate cars to work?
等我们住在一起的时候吧
As soon as we stop living at separate addresses.
-好吧  -我不是催你
- Right. - I mean, I'm not pushing for that.
没有
No.
没事  你可以小催一下
It's okay. You can push a little.
-是吗  -别太急就行
- Oh, really? - Yeah, just a little.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
我叫柯特·邦克  警长
My name is Kurt Bunker, sir.
我是来申请副警长一职的
I'm here to apply for the open deputy position.
逗我呢
Seriously?
我知道我的外表可能让人误会
I understand that my physical appearance may be unsettling,
但我保证  很久之前
but I can assure you my ties
我就与印第安活动没有关系了
to the movement were severed long ago.
不过要除去我身上的纹身
Unfortunately, the removal of my tattoos
需要的时间比预计长了点
has taken longer than anticipated.
戴德郡警署
Dade County Sheriff's Department.
-离佛罗里达不近啊  -我出生在女妖镇
- You're a long way from Florida. - I was born in Banshee.
我认为自己最好
Just became prudent for me
远离以前的圈子
to distance myself from former associates.
那你为什么回来
Then why are you back?
我该回家了  警官
It was time to come home, ma'am.
你以前的朋友对此是什么看法
What do your former associates think about that?
他们怎么看与我无关
What they think is none of my concern.
抱歉  邦克  我们已经有人了
Sorry, Bunker. Position's filled.
这个你留着吧  打扰了
You can hold onto that. I appreciate your time.
他是真想来吗
Was that for real?
我挺喜欢他的
I kind of liked him.
-凯奇先生  -普罗科特先生
- Mr. Cage. - Mr. Proctor.
-你好吗  凯  -很好  谢谢前来
- How are you, Kai? - Good. Thanks for coming.
老友相邀我怎么能不来呢
I couldn't turn down an invitation from an old friend.
这位美女是谁
Who is this pretty young thing?
这是丽贝卡·鲍曼  我侄女
Oh, that's Rebecca Bowman, my niece.
我要让她熟悉一下家族事业
I'm introducing her to the family business.
普罗科特让这高中妞
Proctor pulled the kid out
离开学校来这里学习
of high school for a little show-and-tell.
马丁  怎么说话呢  放尊重点
Martin, watch your mouth. Show a little respect.
抱歉  凯
Sorry, Kai.
话说你找我来干什么
So what was it you wanted to see me about?
老朋友  我们需要重申一下我们的约定
Well, old friend, we need to clarify our arrangement.
什么约定
What arrangement is that?
我的厂子关了三周
While my factory was down for three weeks,
费城的客户是你供的货
you began supplying my Philadelphia customers.
我知道其中的诱惑力  你也是看到了机会
I understand the impulse. You saw an opportunity.
但是我现在重新开张了
But I'm up and running again now,
所以我们以前怎么办现在还怎么办
so we got to go back to things as they were before.
我远离俄亥俄  你也不要打宾夕法尼亚的主意
I stay out of Ohio and you stay out of Pennsylvania.
你没供货  他们就来找我了
You couldn't supply them, they came to me.
仅此而已  只是生意
Plain and simple. Just business.
你搞砸了  普罗科特  哪有要回去的道理
You fucked up, Proctor. You don't get to take that back.
你刚才说什么
What did you just say?
你叔叔在女妖镇可能是个人物
Your uncle may be a big deal here in Banshee,
但是在别人眼里
but in the rest of the world,
他就是个近亲结婚生下的杂种  还目中无人
he's just a country inbreed with an inflated ego.
-马丁  给我闭嘴  -我能处理  爸
- Martin, shut your mouth. - I got it, Dad.
我听说你以前是个厉害人物
Yeah, I heard you were a scary dude back in the day,
-可他现在也不过如此啊  -马丁  闭...
- but he doesn't look so scary now, does he? - Martin, shut--
丽贝卡  不要
Rebecca, no!
善始善终
Finish what you started.
不  不要
No. No.
刚跟斯柏林通完电话
Just got off the phone with Sperling.
普罗科特愿意承认私藏武器
Proctor will plead to a single misdemeanor weapons charge
不想进监狱服刑
in exchange for time served.
-我让他去死了  -同意他的条件
- I told him to go to hell. - Yeah, we'll make the deal.
什么
What?
打电话给斯柏林  告诉他我们...
Call Sperling back and tell him that we'll--
我听到你说什么了
I heard what you said.
那你还问什么
Then why are we still talking about it?
我们有机会解决普罗科特
We've got a shot at putting Proctor away
可你却想妥协  答应他们的条件
and you just want to roll over and play dead.
不  我厌倦了这场毫无希望的战斗
No, I'm done fighting battles I won't win.
你还在嗑药吗
Are you still on the pills?
我已经戒了
No, I'm clean.
我--
So, I--
所以每一秒我都过得很清醒
I get to experience every single moment with total clarity.
不好意思  我得--
Look, if you'll excuse me, I need to--
我得回去继续当市长
I need to get back to being the mayor.
市长的职责又是什么
What does that entail, exactly?
等我搞清楚了会告诉你的
I'll let you know when I figure it out.
谢谢
Thanks.
你让我们去抢军事基地已经够糟了
Bad enough you got us robbing a military base,
我们现在还得
now we got to worry about all
提防亡命徒的追杀
these motherfucking Rambos killing our asses.
上校让海军队员来守着钱
You know, the colonel's got the Marines guarding the money.
他要这些雇佣兵干嘛
What the hell does he need the mercs for?
因为他们保护的可不是美国政府的钱
Cause it ain't Uncle Sam's cash they're protecting.
不是所有事都像童子军一样干净
Turns out not everything is kosher at Boy Scout camp.
公开的记录是  保险柜里有九百万
The official log accounts for nine million in that safe.
那不公开的记录呢
What about the unofficial log?
那就将近一千五百万了
That's saying closer to 15.
有人在做账
Someone's cooking the books.
不是一般人
Not just someone.
道格拉斯·斯通上校
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
作为班里第一名从海军学院毕业
Naval Academy grad, first in his class.
在贝鲁特  巴拿马和海地服过役
Tours in Beirut, Panama, and then Haiti.
之后他挑战了一下人生的其它可能
After that, he took a little walk on the wild side.
他在伊拉克和阿富汗
We're talking about a string of nasty black ops
做了很多血腥的秘密任务
in Iraq and Afghanistan.
这可不是个普通的坏人
This ain't just another bad motherfucker,
这是他们派来
this the guy they send in
杀光其他坏人的坏人
to clean out all the other bad motherfuckers.
换句话说  黑吃黑
On the other hand, you steal from a thief...
不会惊动警察
no one calls the cops.
警察不会带着
The cops won't come after
突击队和阿帕奇直升机来追我们
us with hit teams and Apache helicopters.
这里没人欢迎你
You are not welcome here.
凯
Kai.
请回避一下
你不用来的
You did not have to come.
你发烧了
You have a fever.
只是有点流感而已
It's just a touch of the flu.
喝点水吧
Here, drink some water.
你怎么能任由她病着呢
How can you allow this to go on?
医生来过  也开了药
The doctor was here. He gave her medicine.
她需要的不是家庭医生  她得去医院
She doesn't need a house call. She needs a hospital.
他明天还会来的
He will be here again tomorrow.
我们会问他
We will ask him.
这还不够
But that's not good enough.
-别碰她  -凯
- Leave her! - Oh, Kai.
让开
Get out of my way.
我们能在家照顾好她
We can take care of her here.
你母亲已经是胰腺癌晚期了
Your mother is suffering from advanced pancreatic cancer.
还剩多长时间  医生
How much time, Doctor?
一个月  甚至更短
A month, maybe less.
我要把你放下来了  妈妈
I'm going to put you down, mother.
-你站得住吗  -没问题
- Can you stand? - Yeah.
普罗科特先生  你母亲要死了
Your mother is dying, Mr. Proctor.
你应该开始考虑
You should start thinking
怎样让她好受些
about how you can make her most comfortable.
你还好吗
You okay?
在你回答之前
Before you answer that.
别这样
Don't.
停下
Stop.
停
Stop!
我不能再这样了
I can't do this anymore.
能给我个理由吗
Do I get an explanation?
理由重要吗
Does it really matter?
-你老公  -不是
- Your husband? - No.
-有其他人了  -我没时间给其他人
- Somebody else? - There's no time for anyone else.
我跟你都没时间
There isn't even time for this.
那问题出在哪里
Then what's the problem?
我的孩子们
My kids.
他们需要母亲留在家里
They need their mother at home,
而不是溜出来跟人上床
not sneaking out at night for booty calls.
这跟孩子无关  是你的问题
This isn't about your kids. It's about you.
别说了
Don't do that.
就当做个梦而已  没有其它意义
This is a bubble. This isn't anything.
我们有过的一切很棒
What we had was great,
但我得回到现实世界了
but I've got to get back to the real world.
照顾好自己  好吗
Take care of yourself, okay?
好
All right.
你很喜欢你的军人朋友啊
You really like your military men.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
我还想问你呢
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
我和谁睡都跟你没关系
Who I fuck is none of your business.
影响到工作就和我有关了
It is when it affects the job.
那你和副警长有一腿又怎么算
And how about you getting involved with your deputy sheriff?
那就不影响工作了吗
How does that affect the job?
你跟目标有关系我们就没法抢劫了
We can't do the heist if you're involved with the target.
我已经和他断了  行了吗
I already broke it off. Are we done?
我需要担心吗
Should I be worried?
我说了我会准备好的
I told you I'd be ready.
我不是指工作
I'm not talking about the job.
我得回家了
I gotta get home.
停火
Hold your fire!
阿道夫·希特勒最喜欢的游戏
Adolf Hitler's favorite game
是牛仔对战印第安[对战游戏]
was cowboys and Indians.
他管俄国佬叫红皮肤[印第安人]
He called the Russians redskins
并从白人对我们纳瓦霍族的种族清洗中
and found inspiration in the white man's
得到启发
ethnic cleansing of our Navajo kin.
现在普罗科特屠杀了我们的酋长
Now Proctor has slaughtered our chief
还继续掠夺我们本当拥有的东西
and continues to take what is rightfully ours.
维霍  桑纳
Viho, Songaa.
去把普罗科特和那个女孩抓来
Go get Proctor and the girl.
带他们到这里来
Bring them back here.
应该让我去抓普罗科特
I should be the one getting Proctor.
现在还不是时候
Not now.
我还有别的事要你做
I've got other plans for you.
切顿
Chayton.
这里每个人都觉得我能在这里
Everyone here thinks I get a free ride
是因为我是你的兄弟
'cause I'm your brother.
我要做给他们看看
I need to show them.
你要有耐心
You need to be patient.
艾莉森
Alison.
我需要你在认罪协议上签字
I need your signature on the plea deal
才能提交
before I can file.
请进
Come in.
我在里边加了未来犯罪条款
I included a future crime clause.
就算普罗科特拿了张罚单
If Proctor gets so much as a speeding ticket,
我们也可以撤回认罪协议  重审此案
we can revoke the plea deal and reopen the case.
要喝点什么吗
Can I pour you a drink?
-不用了  -好吧
- I'm fine. - All right.
请自便
Suit yourself.
我喜欢这间新公寓
I like the new apartment.
作为一名律师  你谎撒得真差劲
Yeah, you know, for a lawyer, you're a pretty shitty liar.
好吧  你至少要装一下
Well, you have to at least put in some effort.
把孩子们的房间准备好
Set up the kids' rooms.
挂上些照片
Hang pictures.
在厨房里做顿饭让这里闻起来像个家
Start cooking in the kitchen so it smells like home.
你会做饭吗
Yeah. You cook?
会一点
I dabble.
不如你留下来教教我
Why don't you stick around and teach me?
戈登  我知道你最近经历了一番折磨
Gordon, I know you've been through the wringer,
但是你得振作起来
but you've got to get it together.
-我刚刚有点出格了  -你以为呢
- That was out of line. - You think?
艾莉森  你不用非得走
Alison, look, you don't have to go.
我非常尊敬你
I respect you too much
没办法看你这样作践自己
to watch you embarrass yourself like this.
诺拉
Nola.
我想过你会入乡随俗
You know, I thought you'd gone native,
但是这个
but this...
真是大开眼界
this is a whole new level.
我很高兴你喜欢
I'm glad you like it.
我很高兴你觉得我会喜欢
I'm glad you think I like it.
我想过你会不会回来
I wondered if you'd come back.
我也想过
I wondered the same thing.
每次我觉得我可以摆脱这个鬼地方了
Every time I think I'm rid of this goddamn place--
-这里是你的家  -这是你的家
- This place is your home. - It's your home!
不是我的
It's not mine.
你是奇诺族女人
You are a Kinaho woman.
不知道倒了什么霉要在这里长大
Fat lot of good that did me growing up here.
我知道你以前遭了不少罪
I know you suffered greatly back then.
你以为你知道
You think you know.
-诺拉  -怎么了
- Nola. - What?
让我死了吧
Let me die.
我们在新奥尔良就谈过这个问题了
We already had this conversation in New Orleans.
能别再谈了吗
Can we not do it again?
你已经死了
You're already dead.
你哥哥的事我很抱歉
I'm very sorry about your brother.
-你瞧不起亚历克斯  -我可怜他
- You despised Alex. - I pitied him.
他忘了他是谁  但他的死
He forgot who he was, but his murder
是个悲剧  我们会为他报仇的
was a tragedy and we will avenge it.
所以往普罗科特家派了一群混混吗
By sending a couple of gangbangers to Proctor's house?
他们能处理好
They can handle it.
亚历克斯的死是因为他低估了普罗科特
Alex is dead because he underestimated Proctor.
恕我直言  我不是亚历克斯
With all due respect, I am not Alex.
不  不  你不是
No. No, you're not.
亚历克斯不喜欢你  他认为你会危害到部落
Alex never liked you. He thought you were bad for the tribe.
我就是部落
I am the tribe.
我根本不在乎
Yeah, I really don't care.
诺拉
Nola.
别妨碍我
Don't get in my way.
他是我哥哥  切顿
He was my brother, Chayton.
你会让他们血债血偿的
And you will have your blood.
-但是要听令于你  -没错
- When you say? - Yes.
不
No.
基地下埋着一条古老的汽管隧道
There's an old steam tunnel buried underneath the base.
就像我们的贵宾通道
It's like our own personal VIP entrance.
我们进来了
We're in.
好的  你们要小心点
Okay, now y'all be careful down there.
你懂的  蛇之类的玩意儿
You know, snakes and what not.
你先上
After you.
就像过去一样
Just like old times.
那个保险箱研究得怎么样
So how we doing with the vault?
根据你的描述来看  应该是
Based on your description, it has to be a JT-3000
在弗吉尼亚州定制的JT3000
custom-built in Virginia.
-有几道锁  -两道
- How many locks? - Two.
一道机械锁加一道电子锁
One mechanical, the other digital.
如果我们能破解滚动加密代码
If we get past the rolling encryption code,
我就得在钢筋外壳上钻个六英吋深的洞
I'll have to drill through six inches of reinforced steel
破坏制动系统
to disable the tumbler system.
贾伯能破解密码
Job can handle the encryption code.
-每12分钟变一次  -那我们最好快点
- It changes every 12 minutes. - We'll have to work fast, then.
-你是说我吧  -没错
- And by we, you mean me. - Yep.
-你找我吗  长官  -坐
- You wanted to see me, sir? - Sit.
在阿富汗时  我的小队专门执行黑色行动
My unit was point for black ops in Afghanistan.
回收赃物  抢物资  尽干些脏活
Asset recovery, bag grabs, the dirty stuff.
有天晚上我们受到攻击
One night we came under fire.
还不是什么游兵散将
Not just a couple of insurgents with small arms,
而是一群全副武装的人
dozens of them all armed to the teeth.
有人给他们通风报信
Someone had tipped them off.
我呼叫了空中增援  但迟迟不来
I called for air support, but it never came.
总统的撤军命令意味着
President's troop reductions meant less support
对战场上士兵的增援变少了
for soldiers still on the ground.
只有墨菲和我逃了出来
Murphy and I were the only ones to make it out.
那次袭击让七名好汉
The powers that be let seven good men,
爱国者  因政治而死
patriots, die for politics.
所以我只信任我自己的人
That's why I only trust my people.
这是在你床铺下的地板下找到的
This was found beneath a floorboard under your bunk.
这不是我的
It's not mine.
你是个傻瓜  哈多克
You're an idiot, Haddock.
我本可以让你赚大钱
I could have made you rich
但你却搞砸了  为了什么呢
and you blew it, for what?
-三万元  -长官  我发誓
- 30 grand? - Sir, I swear--
我准你站起来了吗
Did I tell you to stand?
把他关起来
Lock him in the brig.
感觉太容易了
Seems too easy.
可能斯托不知道隧道的事
Maybe Stowe doesn't know about the tunnel.
他知道
He knows.
我们被一扇铁门挡住了
We got a solid steel door blocking us.
有多厚
How thick?
大概12英吋
About 12 inches.
-装药爆破吗  -这不是我的台词吗
- Shape charges? - Now you're talking my language.
等等  如果那些墙壁的牢固性不好
Now hold on. If those walls are not properly reinforced,
你的台词估计会让这个隧道都塌了
your language will bring down the whole damn tunnel.
你想怎么办
What do you suggest?
我会把门的铰链拆了
Look, I'll pull the door off the hinges
比较老式的办法
the old-fashioned way.
说的好像你还知道别的方法似的
Like you got any other motherfucking way.
报告  所有房间安全
Checking in. All rooms secure.
去找普罗科特
Go find Proctor.
我饿死了
I'm starving.
冰箱里有些肉馅土豆馅饼
There's some shepherd's pie in the fridge.
牛肉的还是火鸡的
Ooh, beef or turkey?
我已经不吃红肉了
I stopped eating red meat.
你也应该这么做
You should, too.
那不可能
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
这样吧
You know what?
我去做点吃的
I'll make us something to eat.
做点三文治我们吃
I'll make us some sandwiches.
你这有午餐肉吗  冷切肉呢
You got some lunch meat? Some cold cuts?
布罗克  你当前在什么位置  完毕
Brock, what's your current location, over?
不要  她可以找别人的
Don't. She'll find somebody else.
我还在工作  给我
I'm still on duty. Give it to me.
-别管了...  -快点给我
- Just let it-- - Come on, give it to me.
-我没跟你开玩笑  小艾  -不要
- I'm not messing around, Em. - Come on.
靠
Damn it!
这是布罗克  请讲  阿尔玛
Uh, yeah, this is Brock. Go ahead, Alma.
接到普罗科特家的骚乱报警
We got a call of a disturbance at the Proctor place.
有人员伤亡
Casualties reported.
收到  马上到
Copy that. I'm on my way.
工作还是第一哈
Job still comes first, huh?
-别这样  -跟过去一样
- Come on. - Just like the old days.
小艾
Em.
你想要我怎样
What do you want from me?
我想要你离开
I want you to leave.
跟你说
You know what?
你想啥来啥
You're in luck.
需要把所有东西都拍给我看
I need pictures of everything.
告诉她这次一定要集中注意力
Tell her to keep it in focus this time.
我能听到你说话  贾伯
I can hear you, Job.
我知道
Oh, I know.
等一下
Hold on one second.
-胡德  -我  布罗克
- Hood. - Hey, it's Brock.
在普罗科特家的泳池里找到一名DOA
Look, we got a DOA in Proctor's pool.
Dead on arrival  送达医院已经死亡
红骨帮  看样子他和他的小伙伴
Redbone. Looks like he and
把人家侄女折腾够呛
his buddy roughed up the niece pretty bad.
我马上过去  我得走了
I'm on my way. I gotta go.
你得走了是他妈什么意思
Fuck you mean you gotta go?
我还在上班
I'm still on duty.
安娜会干完这里的活
Ana will finish up down here.
宝贝  这假警长的破事
Baby, this whole fake sheriff bullshit
已经耽误你真正的工作了
is getting in the way of your real job.
-听到没  -努力不听
- You hear me? - Hard not to.
你还好吗
You all right?
布罗克  给我一分钟
Hey, Brock. Give us a minute.
警长
Sheriff.
你干掉朗西德的时候  这场战争就开始了
You started this war when you took out Longshadow.
是的  开战了你会知道的  警长
Yeah, well, you would know about starting wars, Sheriff.
切顿还是会来找你的
Chayton's not gonna stop coming for you.
那是切顿不走运了
That's unfortunate for Chayton
任何来找我的人都一样
and anyone else who comes after what's mine.
我跟你说明白
Okay, let me be clear.
你们两边斗成什么样是你们的事
You and the Redbones can tear each other apart.
老子不管  他妈的给我快点
I don't give a shit. Just hurry the fuck up.
我家被这些下等人侵犯了
My house was violated by these lowlifes.
干好你的活  警长
You do your job, Sheriff.
雷文  过来
Hey, Raven. Come here.
你了解居留地  从哪开始
You know the reservation. Where do we start?
我们不能就这么去居留地
We can't just go to the reservation.
我们可以  我一直都这样
Yeah, we can. I do it all the time.
就是这儿了
This is it?
对  铁钩镇
Yep, Dog Iron.
这里有很多红骨帮的人
A lot of Redbones hang out here.
酒便宜  还不会有人来找麻烦
Drinks are cheap and nobody bothers them.
看看我们能做什么吧
Hmm, well, let's see what we can do about that.
铁沟镇酒吧
给我们来点酒
Can we get a couple of drinks?
行  这条路再走三公里
Sure, three miles down the road.
你好  苏
Hey, Sue.
比利  你知道不该穿这身制服来
Billy, you know better than to show up here in that uniform.
你就告诉我有没有看到切顿吧
Then just tell me if you've seen Chayton.
-滚出去  -有人在受伤
- Get the hell out of here. - People are getting hurt.
我们的人
Our people.
我只知道他们在丛林深处
All I know is that they're deep in the woods.
丛林深处什么地方
Where abouts in the woods?
-你得走了  -雷文
- You gotta go. - Yo, Raven.
谢谢你
Thanks for your time.
你觉得你老爹要是知道
What do you think your old man would say
你听一个白小子的命令  他会说什么
if he knew you were taking orders from the white man?
-让开  斯派奇  -不然呢
- Move, Spatch. - Or what?
你一定要玩这套吗
You sure that's how you want to play this?
你的警徽
Your, uh, badge...
在这屁都不是
don't mean shit around here.
警徽是你最不用担心的
Well, the badge is the last thing you should worry about.
此话怎讲
How's that?
他妈的给我坐下
Sit the fuck down.
都别闹了好么
How about we all put our dicks away?
见到你也很高兴  艾米
It's good to see you, too, Aimee.
搞什么啊  比利
What the hell, Billy?
善终服务的护士来了
The hospice nurse is here.
-普罗科特先生  -洛特斯女士
- Mr. Proctor. - Ms. Lotus.
时间紧  谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
大家对你的评价很高
You came highly recommended, you know.
请叫我艾米丽
Please, call me Emily.
好的  艾米丽
All right, Emily.
请像在自己家里一样
Why don't you make yourself at home here?
需要什么尽管说
And anything you need, just ask.
先把我介绍给你母亲好吗
Why don't you start by introducing me to your mother?
这位是莉亚  我母亲  还有瑞贝卡  我侄女
This is Leah, my mother, and Rebecca, my niece.
很高兴见到你们
It's a pleasure to meet you both.
艾米丽会和我们住在一起  妈妈
Emily will be staying with us, Mother,
来照顾你
to help care for you.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我  我发生了意外
I-- I had an accident.
你有给伤口上药吗
Well, have you put anything on those cuts?
没有
No.
给你
Here.
它会防止伤口结疤
It'll help keep you from scarring.
-你的皮肤很好  -谢谢你
- You've got great skin. - Thank you.
让我带你看看你的房间
Let me show you to your room.
诺提  斯派奇找我们茬儿
Notie and Spatch were looking for a fight.
找事的是你们
You were looking for a fight.
穿着女妖镇的警服来这儿干嘛
What are you thinking going to the Dog Iron in a BSD uniform?
-他是跟着我来的  -我没跟你说话
- He was following me. - I wasn't talking to you.
我们在找切顿·里特斯通
We're looking for Chayton Littlestone.
-你认识他吗  -他是认真的吗
- You know him? - Is he serious?
-我们一起的  -滚出保留地  比利
- We're on the same side here. - Get off the res, Billy.
如果雅兹发现你在这儿
If Yaz finds out that you're out here--
等等  雅兹是谁
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Who's Yaz?
卡尔·雅兹  奇诺警局的警长
Karl Yazzie. Chief of the Kinaho PD.
听起来我应该见见这人
Sounds like someone I should meet.
我们走  我带你去
Let's go. I'll take you.
不  识相的话  你应该
No, you should probably get in your car
钻进车里  赶紧离开
and drive away if you know what's good for you.
我看起来像是识相的人吗
Do I look like someone who knows what's good for him?
警长
Chief.
你一定是来错地方了  小子
You must have made a wrong turn, boy.
这里是奇诺警署
This is the Kinaho Police Department.
-这位是谁  -卢卡斯·胡德警长
- And who do we have here? - Sheriff Lucas Hood.
就是你逮捕了杀柯利瑞的混蛋
You busted that fat bastard that killed the Cleary girl.
我很惊讶你知道这事
I'm surprised you know about that,
那就是你懒得帮忙了
seeing as you didn't lift a finger to help.
是在你的辖区发生的  不是我的
Happened on your beat, not mine.
我只管好我辖区的事
I stay on my side of the line.
好吧  切顿和红骨帮
Okay, well, Chayton and the Redbones,
他们洗劫了一辆热那亚基地的军车
they hijacked a truck from Camp Genoa.
偷了大概十二箱的AK和M4
Stole about a dozen crates of AKs and M4s.
-什么  何时发生的  -听起来是军方的事
- What? When? - Sounds like a military issue.
如果枪在女妖镇出现  就归我管
Not if the guns end up in Banshee.
抱歉  我不知道他在哪里
Sorry, I can't tell you where the man is if I don't know.
但我们会留意他的
But we'll keep an eye out for him.
你们会留意的
You'll keep an eye out?
事不关己  是吧
None of your business, huh?
-我们走  -还有件事  警长
- Let's go. - Oh, one other thing, Sheriff.
-什么  -出于礼貌我叫你警长
- Yeah? - I call you sheriff as a courtesy,
即使你在这儿什么都不是
even though out here you've got no standing.
下次你再搞出今天这样的屁事
The next time you pull some shit like you did today,
我就报告印第安事务局  烦死你
I'm gonna have BIA crawling all over your ass.
咱还是各管各的吧
You mind your own backyard and we'll mind ours.
比利
Billy.
你也一样
That goes for you, too.
雅兹是坏警察吗
So Yaz is dirty?
不是
No.
他没那么有野心
That would actually require ambition.
他只是很久以前就放弃了
Yazzie gave up on that a long time ago.
部落议会和红骨帮
Between the tribal council and the Redbones,
他都不得罪
he's everyone's bitch.
-那个姑娘呢  -艾米吗  她是个狠角色
- What about the girl? - Aimee? She's the real deal.
她只是不想碌碌无为
She just wants to make a difference.
她不太喜欢你
She doesn't like you much.
对  她觉得我抛弃了她
Yeah, she feels I abandoned her.
她做的对
She's not wrong.
不过我得把家人救出来
But I had to get my family out.
你有孩子
You got kids?
对  俩女儿
Yeah, two little girls.
蕾切尔和金姆
Rachel and Kim.
你呢
You?
我没孩子
No. No kids.
珍妮
Jenny.
市长先生
Mr. Mayor.
客厅还是卧室呢
Living room or bedroom?
今天还是算了...
I think I'm gonna, um--
我很累...
I'm-- I'm really tired. I--
我肯定能让你精神
I bet I can wake you up.
不  珍妮
No, Jenny.
我不该叫你来的
Look, I shouldn't have called you.
麻烦你了
For your trouble.
明天再试试吗
Try again tomorrow?
不必了  我们到此为止吧
No, I-- I think this is the end of the road for us.
好吧  如果改变主意
Well, if you change your mind,
随时来找我
you know where you can find me.
我们打烊了
Kitchen's closed, men.
没事  我们吃过了
That's all right. We already ate.
我还以为你这样的人被女人揍了
I would think after a guy like you got his ass kicked by a woman,
绝对不会
the last thing he'd want to do
带朋友来再感受一遍呢
is bring his friends over to watch it happen again.
小嘴倒是挺利的  婊子
You got a smart mouth on you, bitch.
他们都这么说
So I hear.
今晚我就让你再也张不开嘴
I'm gonna shut it for you tonight permanently.
听着
Listen,
我今天很累了  懒得跟你嘴炮
it's been a long day and I'm all out of repartee.
你要是来打架的
So if you came here to fight,
就别娘泡似的瞎逼逼  赶紧动手
quit whining like a little girl and get right down to it.
-这是怎么了  -别管  波卡洪塔斯
- What's going on here? - Get lost, Pocahontas.
-不关你事  -我一般不会插手
- Ain't none of your business. - Normally, I'd agree.
可你如果找她麻烦
But if you're messing with the only person
我就不能坐视不理了
who can serve me some of that apple pie,
毕竟她做的苹果派无人能敌
then I'm afraid it is my concern.
我给你三秒钟  扭着你的小翘臀
I'll give you three seconds to walk your pretty little ass
滚出去  否则我...
out that door before I--
别说我的屁股
Don't talk about my ass.
能给我做个派吗
So, how about that pie?
没问题
You got it.
-你是亚历克斯·朗西德的妹妹  -我是诺拉
- You're Alex Longshadow's sister. - Nola.
你是纽约犯罪集团老大的女儿
And you're the New York mobster's daughter.
我叫卡莉  你哥哥的事我很遗憾
Carrie. Sorry about your brother.
你的人生我也很遗憾
Sorry about your life.
你戴的是什么  挺好看  格洛克枪吗
Those are nice. What are they, Glocks?
改良过的17C
Modified 17Cs.
射速能达到每分钟1200发
Cycle at 1,200 rounds per minute.
恩  我更喜欢M1903
Mmm, more of a Springfield girl myself.
感觉不一样
Different strokes.
派很好吃  是这里做的吗
That's a great pie. They bake it here?
我理应回答得上来
I should know the answer to that.
但我不知道
I don't.
不过我知道苏格兰威士忌在哪里
I do know where they keep the scotch.
敬父辈的罪行
Sins of the fathers.
阿门
Amen.
我  想来看看你
I, um, thought we could hang out.
你不该来
You shouldn't really be here.
你不用上学吗
Don't you have school?
是啊
Yeah.
也是
好吧  那放学以后呢
Okay, so then after school?
-我可以去凯迪店  -不  蒂法
- I can come by the Cadi. - No, Deva--
-你不是想了解我吗  -是啊
- Don't you want to get to know me? - Yes.
那为啥不呢
Then why won't you?
我知道你现在想不通
Look, I know this is confusing for you,
但是戈登养大了你  他很爱你
but Gordon raised you, he loves you,
他是你的父亲
he's your father.
那你呢
And what about you?
你说你留在女妖镇是为了我
You told me you stayed in Banshee because of me.
我是想确保你没事
I had to make sure you were okay.
我有事
I'm not.
操
Fuck!